前情提要
Previously on The Mob Doctor...
只要你还在芝加哥，你就欠我的，一言为定
As long as you're in Chicago,I own you. That's the deal.
我听说你想接手莫拉提的生意
So, I hear you want to take over Moretti's deal with us.
对，没错
Yeah, that's right.
不可能
Ain't gonna happen.
我知道怎么两头拿钱
I know about the double dipping.
我们从艾尔的投币机生意中抽25%
Our cut's 25% al on the machines.
你就想要15%
You were asking for 15%.
我的兄弟们不会答应的
My brother's not gonna like this.
赛莱斯特，康斯坦汀
Celeste.Constantine.
你真觉得联合财团是个好主意吗？
You really think uniting the syndicate is a good thing?
是的，这是个潘多拉魔盒
I do.It's a Pandora's Box.
开会吧
Let's get this meeting started.
你要是不小心点
And if you're not careful,
你就又得蹲监狱，或者更糟
You'll end up back in jail --or worse.
康斯坦丁来了，你得赶紧走
Constantine's coming.You have to leave.
听我说，我刚回到你身边，不想现在就走
Listen to me. I just got you back.
There's no way I'm running now.
没有别的办法，你现在必须得走了
There is no other way.
You have to go -- now.
真的，没事，你尝尝
Look -- I don't care.Take a bite.
吃吧，巧克力吃起来感觉不怎么样
Go on. Take a bite.The chocolate tastes cheap.
我不想在我的潘趣卷里放便宜巧克力
I-I-I don't want to have cheap
chocolate on my punsch rolls.
斯塔沃斯，过来帮我尝尝这个
Stavos. Come over here and taste something for me.
挺好吃的
Tastes good.
我想要的是芝加哥最好的潘趣卷
I want the best-tasting damn punsch rolls in Chicago.
多花点钱用比利时黑巧克力做
Spend the extra buck and get the belgian dark.
你知道蛋糕店只是个掩护吗？
The bakery's just a front,you know?
这是用来洗钱的是吗？
Cash business to launder our money, right?
我父亲曾经说过
Like my old man said,
如果你想做事，就得把事情做好
If you're gonna do something,do it right.
说到把事情做好
Speaking of doing things right,
阿马特斯的游戏机保护费又交晚了
The Amatos are late with their gaming-machines cut again.
你给泰塔斯打电话
You call Titus.
告诉他每晚交一天我就多收一个百分点
You tell him I'm gonna take a point for every day he's late.
你有客人来了
looks like you have a visitor.
小赛
Celeste.
郊区的生意你要给特拉帕尼50%的抽成
You're giving Trapani 50% of our downtown action.
对呀，你承诺给我的也是50%
That's right.You promised me 50%.
对呀
Also right.
你把所有的钱都给我们了
So, if you're giving away all the money,
你自己还剩下什么呀？
Then what's left for you?
嘿，我给弄杯咖啡或者小蛋糕吧？
Hey, can I get you an espresso or a cupcake?
这儿的潘趣卷做得一般
I don't recommend the punsch rolls.
你给我解释解释
I'd like an explanation,Constantine.
哦
Oh.
嘿，哥儿几个，你们先出去一下
Hey, fellas,give me a couple minutes.
西城和北城的生意都拿50%
The West Side and the North Side are both gonna get 50%.
我一向说话算数
I always keep my word.
那南城就什么都没有吗？你什么也不拿？
And the South Side gets nothing? You get nothing?
接管了郊区的生意
Well, you know,taking over downtown
我收获的可不仅仅是钱
Means a lot more to me than money.
你觉着我能信你这话吗？
you expect me to believe that?
艾尔・卡彭来之后就一直没弄完
Well, it hasn't been done since Al Capone.
你太自负了吧
So, this is about your ego.
随便你怎么说
You call it what you want.
对我来说，这就是在创造历史
To me,it's about making history.
咱们把这个盒子打开
Hey, what do you say...We crack this box open,
喝点儿香槟酒，你帮我拿点冰块来怎么样？
We put this nice champagne you gave me on ice.
啊？
What?
你今儿早上送我的香槟啊
The bottle of champagne you sent me this morning.
老康，我没给你送过香槟
Tino, I didn't send that to you.
那是谁送的？
Then who did?
你干吗呀？
What are you doing?
这里边装了一个压板
It's rigged with a pressure plate.
在这儿呢
Here we go.
你最好出去等一会
You better wait outside.
家庭作业――用超声波
Take-home message --use the ultrasound
预测病人体内的脓液流动状态
To estimate fluid status in septic patients
观察呼吸以判断下静脉腔是否破裂
By looking at the IVC collapse with respiration.
最后一个作业，患者满意度调查
And one last thing --patient-satisfaction surveys.
伯德做得很认真
Board takes them seriously.
我建议你们也认真对待
I suggest that you do, too.
喂？你讲义的第三页
Hello? Page three of your handouts,
有新的规定，今天就要落实
You find a new script being implemented today.
鲁滨逊大夫
Dr. Robinson.
你好，我是布兰克医生
"hello,my name is Dr. Blank.
这是我的名片
"here's my card.
抱歉让你久等了，布兰克马上就来
I am sorry you had to wait blank minutes to see me."
我再给你拿个枕头或者被子吧？
"can I offer you an extra pillow or blanket?"
我们是医生还是服务员？
Are we surgeons or room service?
每个医生都要接受
Any doctor receiving three failing grades
一个月三次的医患态度检查
Within a month will be attending
the bedside-manner seminar.
好，我这就来
All right, on my way.
急诊室五分钟之后要来一个特重病人
We got a V.I.P.Five minutes out from the E.R.
今天谁值班？我
Who's on trauma call? I am.
好吧，你跟我来，鲁滨逊，你也来
All right, you're with me.Dr. Robinson, you, too.
我已经被安排在术后检查门诊了
I'm scheduled for post-op clinic.
你被抽调了，已经通知前台广播了
Not anymore.The paramedics radioed ahead.
病人点名让你来治疗
The patient requested you by name.
是谁呀？咱们会知道的
Who's the patient? We're about to find out.
自行车事故，28岁，男性
cycling accident. 28-year-old male.
头部损伤导致神志不清
Head injury with altered mental status.
右手腕部骨折，急性知觉丧失
Open right wrist fracture A.L.O.C.（Acute Loss of Consciousness）
气象色谱标准10，体征稳定
GCS 10.Vitals stable.
胸前端和手足损伤
Abrasions to anterior chest and extremities.
这是谁呀？
Who is he?
杰克・汉森――联邦检察官的儿子
Jack Hanson --U.S. Attorney's son.
他为什么点名让你治疗？你认识他？
Why would he ask for you? You know him?
对，他是我弟弟
Yeah.He's my brother.
合金钢管，橡胶雷管
Galvanized-metal pipe.Rubber blasting caps.
把钳子递给我
Hand me those pliers.
好的
All right.
老康，可能是短的那根
Tino,there could be a short.
嘘，别说话
Shh. Quiet.
现在我们要做的
Now all we got to do...
就是找出是谁要杀我
...Is figure out who's trying to kill me.
炸弹解除了
It's disarmed.
谢天谢地
thank God.
那么，到底谁想杀你？
So,who wants you dead?
现在？猜猜看
Nowadays? Pick a number.
我手下的姑娘认识一个炸弹专家
One of my girls has a regular on the bomb squad.
我可以找他帮忙
I could ask him to take a look at the device,
没准能找出是谁送的炸弹
Maybe help us figure out who sent it.
那，你觉得你找的这个人
Well, do you think you can trust this guy
能保守秘密吗？
To keep his mouth shut?
我手里有他的把柄
I have a video of him in a compromising position.
好吧
Yeah.
你让他动作快一点
Well, you tell him to work quick.
因为甭管是谁送的炸弹，他还会再有新的行动
Because whoever did this --they're gonna try again.
Subtitle by @godort
《黑帮天使》第一季 第11集 “手足相残”
The Mob Doctor Season 1, Episode 11, "Sibling Rivalry"
汉森先生，握我的手
Mr. Hanson, squeeze my hand!
没反应
Non-responsive.
如果杰克・汉森是你弟弟，那马克・汉森就是……
If Jack Hanson is your brother,then Mark Hanson --
就是我爸爸
Is my father.
*******我只是退出了痛苦的刺激
Only withdraws to painful stimuli.
你们不同姓？
Different last name?
随我妈的姓，我在上大学的时候改的
It's my mother's maiden name.I changed it during college.
咱待会再说这个行么？
Can we talk about this later?
放一思达清理肾功能
Run an I-stat to clear his renal function,
先给他扫描
Then pan-scan him --priority one.
苏西说的对
Susie is right.
我得把他推到放射科去
I'll roll him to radiology.
不行，病人家属不能参与治疗
No, he's a family member.
你可以看着，但从现在开始不能插手
You can observe.But from here on, hands off.
德芙琳大夫，你的VIP病人怎么样了？
Dr. Devlin,how's your V.I.P. Patient?
他没有生命危险
His vitals are stable.
很好，我需要你参加一个外科会诊
Good. I need you for a surgical consult.
走吧
Let's go.
药的副作用
Bounce-back，lower-right quadrant pain.
让她右下腹疼痛
Medicine turfed her to us.
开玩笑呢吧
you're joking.
你认识伊文斯夫人？
You already know Ms. Evans?
她经常到这来拿药
She's a frequent flyer.She's here for drugs.
我得提醒你
Let me remind you that you've already received
你已经有两次服务态度差评了，所以
Two failing grades on the patient surveys, so --
弗拉尼根大夫，这只是一个创伤复查
Dr. Flanigan,it was a wound recheck
谁会因为我正做的阑尾切除术急呢
Who got mad that I was busy with a ruptured appy...
大夫，还有给粪便栓塞做直肠检查
Doctor... And a fecal impaction who resented the rectal exam.
大夫
Doctor.
这是她的病例
Her chart is up and loaded.
嘿，伊文斯小姐，我是德芙琳大夫
Hi, Miss Evans. I'm Dr. Devlin.
对，我记得你
Yeah. I remember you.
抱歉让你久等了
Sorry you had to wait so long.
我他妈都等了几个小时了
four damn hours.
等死我了
could have died.
那么，你的下腹部疼痛
So, you have pain in your lower abdomen.
对吗？
Is that right?
对，好吧，我看一下
Yeah.Okay, may I?
好
Yeah.
听着，我需要点止疼药
Look, I'm gonna -- I'm gonna need something for the pain.
我对布洛芬，酮类和吗啡过敏
I'm allergic to ibuprofen,ketorolac, and morphine.
嗯
Mm.
有一种D打头的药
There's this other drug,"d"-something.
盐酸氢吗啡酮？
Dilaudid?
对，对
Yeah.Yeah.
你的病征有点轻微扩散
You have mild,diffuse tenderness.
没有反弹，没有保护
No rebound, no guarding.
股动脉很正常
Strong femoral pulses.
是啊，这真是好消息
Yeah, this is really all good news.
你聋了吗？
Are -- are you deaf?
我刚才说很疼
I -- I said it hurts.
你知道你们医院的规定吗？
Are you familiar with your own hospital's policy?
你说什么？听着
Excuse me? Look.
你得给我做个CT
You need to order me a C.T.,
还得给我拿点止疼药
And the you need to get me something for the pain.
行了，伊文斯小姐，你每年到医院来八十一次
Okay, Miss Evans,you've actually been here
每次都有新的病征
81 times this year,each time with a new complaint.
再给你多做几次CT
Give you any more C.T.s,
你的卵巢就该有阴影了
Your ovaries are gonna start glowing in the dark.
我知道，但是这次情况不一样
Yeah, but this --it's different this time.
那么，我将遵守医院的规定
So, I am gonna follow hospital policy
把你转给一位药物依赖专家
And I'm gonna refer you to a drug-addiction specialist.
不行
I don't --I don't need that.
让专家帮你吧
please, get some help.
谢谢你
Thank you.
嘿，内特
Hey, Nate.
格蕾丝，你能出来吗？
Grace.Can you get away?
哦，我正在等化验结果
Um, I'm waiting on some test results. What's going on?
求你了，这事很严重，你必须过来一趟
Please, it's important.You got to get over here.
那好吧
Okay, fine.
哦，我时间不多
Uh, I just don't have much time, though.
我把地址发给你
I'm texting you the address.
咱们得快点
We got to hurry.
为什么叫我到这儿来好吗？我把事情搞砸了，
Tell me why I'm here, Nate.I screwed up, okay?
我知道上回说不让你帮忙了，可是这回我需要你
I-I know what I said before,but I need your help.
跟我来好吗？
Just follow me, okay?
要是有紧急情况，你就应该报警
If you have an emergency,you call 911.
除了你我谁也不能告诉
I can't call anybody except you!
为什么
Why not?
格蕾丝
Grace...
来见见马蒂小子
Meet Matty Boy.
马
A horse.
纯种赛马
Thoroughbred racehorse.
我又不是兽医
Do I look like a vet?
我要真找一兽医来他就报警了
No, a vet would call the cops.
你是谁？
Who are you?
格蕾丝，这是维克多
Grace, Victor.
为什么不能让警察知道？
Call the cops for what?
这不是我们的马
It's not our horse.
马蒂小子赢过阿灵顿比赛
Matty Boy won the Arlington Cup.
他的精子价值十万美元
His sperm is worth 100 grand.
精子？
His sperm?
他怎么勃起了？
Why does he have an erection?
我们想取点他的精液卖钱
We were trying to get his sperm.
但是他不肯合作
But he wasn't cooperating.
我们给他找的充气娃娃可能不合他的胃口
Our, uh --our dummy mare wasn't his type.
所以，维克多决定给他来点伟哥
So, Vic decides to give him a handful of Viagra,
结果它就再也软不下来了
And now it won't go down.
这马明天还有一场比赛
The horse has got to race tomorrow.
我得走了
Yeah, I got to go.
求你了，格蕾丝
Grace, please.
有患者需要我，内特，人类患者
I have patients who need me, Nate -- people patients.
这马是维克多的老板汤姆・沃斯的
The horse belongs to Vic's boss,Tommy Walls.
汤姆是海德公园帮的老大
Tommy's a captain with the Hyde Park crew.
是，我知道他是谁
Yeah,I know who he is.
他可不是你惹得起的人
And he's not the kind of guy that you mess with.
维克多负责马的运输工作
Vic's in charge of the horse's transport.
它原来是很容易拿到冠军的
It was gonna be an easy score.
求你了，帮帮我吧
Please! Help me out.
要是汤姆知道我们干了什么，我们俩就全完了
If Tommy finds out what we did,we're both dead.
卡罗尔，哦，布雷特
Carol. Oh, Brett.
嘿
Hey.
你弟弟怎么样了？还昏迷着呢
How's your brother? Still unconscious.
我们正在评估他的头部创伤
We're assessing the extent of his head trauma.
他撞车的时候我看见了
I was there, you know,when he crashed.
我们在法院参加一个听证会
We were meeting at the courthouse for a hearing,
他第一次当上合伙人
His first since making partner.
杰克当合伙人啦？
Jack's a partner?
是啊，都合伙人好几个礼拜了
Yeah, three weeks now.
是挺快的，我知道，但是你爸爸一定很会说服人
It's quick, I know, but your father can be persuasive.
是啊，这像是我爸的风格
Yeah, sounds like dad.
你给家里人打过电话吗？
Have you called your family?
医院给安娜贝尔打电话了，她正在路上
The hospital alerted Annabelle.She's on her way.
那你爸爸呢？
And what about your father?
我不知道
I -- I don't know.
我给他打个电话，好的
I'll call him. Okay.
小罗，谢天谢地
Ro, thank God.
我那了点酸苹果
I got Granny Smith
和医务科里所有能找到的间羟异丁肾上腺素
And all the terbutaline we had in the med room.
我在药瓶上写了“过期销毁”
I marked the bottles "expired and destroyed."
谢谢你
thank you.
你知道我爱你对吗？
You know I love you,right?
是啊，我可以解释
Yeah, I can explain.
别解释
Please, don't.
好吧，谢谢
Okay, thanks.
你干吗呢？
What are you doing?
间羟异丁肾上腺素是治疗人类持续勃起症的
Terbutaline treats priapism in humans.
马是哺乳动物，兴许管用
A horse is a mammal.So hopefully, it will work.
嘿，嘿
Hey, there. Hey.
现在怎么办？
Now what?
等着并且祈祷吧
You wait and you pray.
用李子干吗？
What's with the plums?
在监狱里
In prison,some of the guys
有人用它造酒
Used to make a little hooch out of it.
把李子绞碎，掺上点糖
Take a plum,mix it with some sugar.
结果有一天，造酒这人被抓住了
Anyway, one day,the guys got caught,
最后典狱长就把李子禁了一整年
And the warden banned plums for an entire year.
我不知道你还是这方面的行家
I didn't know you were such a fan.
我可不是
I'm not.
但那时候我否认知道这个方法，那就是我想要的
But the moment I was denied, that's all I wanted.
嗯，有客人来了
Hmm.Here comes tweedledum.
泰塔斯
Titus.
你好吗，老兄
How you doing,buddy?
嘿，你知道有个罗马皇帝跟你同名吗？
Hey, did you know there's a roman emperor with your name?
泰塔斯・奥古斯塔斯。哦，是吗？
Titus Augustus.Oh, yeah?
我问问你
Let me ask you something --
到目前为止你有多少机器交货了？
How many machines you delivered so far?
我没仔细数。我数了
I don't have an exact count. I do.
117台，应该是500台
117.It's supposed to be 500.
生产上有点延迟
There's a slight manufacturing delay.
我们要是缺货，竞争对手就会先于我们抢走生意
If we're short, our competition gets the jump on us.
那会让我们损失几百万
It'll cost us millions.
我心里有数
I'm handling it.
好的，我希望你不要胡来
Yeah, well, I hope you're not messing around.
我的意思是，大家都知道你和你的兄弟……
I mean, we all know that you and your brother --
觉得挣得太少了
You weren't happy with the price.
那么，别胡来
Well,don't screw around.
是，我不知道，你这个偏执狂
Yeah. I don't know.You're paranoid.
思达沃斯，你给评评理
Stavos, talk some sense into your boss.
听着，我们在同一条船上
Listen,we're in this together, right?
你如果需要我们的帮你
You need us to help you with that, uh,
改善生产效率什么的，就说话
Manufacturing delay,you say the word.
对啊，还有保安什么的
Yeah, security,anything you need.
我用不着帮助，我告诉你们俩
I don't need any help.I'm telling you guys.
在截止日前我会造出那些机器的
I'm gonna have the machines for you by the end of the week.
嘿，你弟弟怎么样了？
Hey.How's your brother?
杰克的脾脏破裂了
Jack's got a splenic fracture
伴有脓液流出
With extravasation and free fluids.
他需要把脓液排出去
He needs an ex-lap.
他现在已经准备好去做手术了
He's being prepped for surgery right now.
怀特医生让我来做术前清理
Dr. White asked me to scrub in.
我妈的葬礼之后我就没见过我弟弟
I hadn't seen my brother since my mom's funeral.
你们俩吵架啦？
You guys had a falling out?
没有，因为我爸爸
No. It's my dad.
我们意见不合
We don't really see eye-to-eye.
哦，真遗憾
Oh, I'm sorry.
父亲会比较强硬
Fathers can be tough.
是啊，他查处了两个腐败官员
Yeah, but, you know, mine put away two corrupt governors,
这就让他变成了英雄，是吧？
So that kind of makes him a hero, right?
这让他的工作很顺利
It makes him good at his job.
我妈曾经说过
My mom used to say
每个伟人的背后都有一颗自负的心
That behind every great man is an even greater ego.
嘿，我得去做手术去了。
Hey, I'm gonna head to the surgery, okay?
你且不走呢吧？
You'll be around later?
对
Yeah.
好
Okay.
布雷特怎么样？
How's Brett holding up?
我觉得他还好吧
Fine. I think.
报一下脾损伤情况，大夫？
Grade the spleen injury,doctor?
非侵害性，
Non-invasive,subcapsular hematoma
囊下血肿占表面的50%
Involving over 50% surface area,
40%血供应阻断――第四阶段
40% devascularization --grade 4.
很准确，那么我们……
Exactly. So, we...
做一个德克松网状包裹脾脏修复术
Do a dexon mesh wrap splenorrhaphy --
挽救脾脏
Save the spleen.
好，第一步，动员
Good. First step --mobilization.
等会儿，心率加快了
Hold on.B.P.'s falling fast.
别是从脾伤出来的，已经不能再失血了
Can't be from the spleen injury.
There's not enough blood loss.
先别给他灌注了，他的心率太快了
He's not perfusing.B.P.'s cratering.
可能是肺部栓塞了，加大氧分压
Could have thrown a pulmonary embolism. Increase the PO2.
加大生理盐水
Open the saline wide.
妈的！到五了，胺碘酮指数，150
Damn it. Run of five.Amiodarone, 150.
好吧，先别做修复了
All right,screw the repair.
我们得赶紧抓住肝脏
We got to grab the spleen and run.
眼底有反应了
Disconjugate,doll's-eyes movements.
他的腿受刺激后能动了，但胳膊还动不了
He's moving his legs in response to stimuli but not his arms.
这倒新鲜了，他入院的时候还是胳膊对都能动呢
That's new. He came in moving extremities times four.
那么，头部创伤导致了进行性麻痹
So, he's showing progressive paralysis following head trauma.
鉴别诊断是什么？
What's the differential diagnosis?
脊髓化验呈阴性，也许是脊髓中心压迫综合征？
Spinal C.T. was negative.Maybe... Central Cord Syndrome?
颈脊髓损伤？做核磁共振检查
Sciwora? Need an MRI.
嗯，他现在还不够稳定
Eh, he's not stable enough.
机能损伤都有哪些？
What do we know about the mechanism of injury?
胸部和四肢擦伤，腕骨破裂
Chest and extremity abrasions.Wrist fracture.
好了，那就是说得做面部移植
All right,which suggests face-plant.
做宫颈末端弯曲和扩张的检查了吗？
Could there have been extreme
cervical flection or extension?
卡罗尔可能知道
Carol might know.
他是杰克的公司的资深合伙人
She's a senior partner at Jack's firm.
她看见他被撞了
She was there.She saw him go down.
我应该跟她谈谈。好吧，行
I could talk to her.All right, fine.
好，叫上格蕾丝
Okay.Take Grace.
威尔科克斯医生，你好吗？
Dr. Wilcox.How's your day?
正在做胆囊HIDA扫描
Well, the gall bladder is getting a hida scan,
我正要去咖啡厅吃一个蓝莓松饼
And I am going to the cafeteria hoping for a blueberry muffin.
等会再去吧，我需要你参加一个会诊
That can wait. I need your help with a surgical consult.
那不是格蕾丝的病人吗？
Isn't she Grace's patient?
格蕾丝让她出院，结果她在大厅里打电话报警了
Grace discharged her, but she called 911 from the lobby.
医护人员把她带回急诊室了
Paramedics brought her back to the E.R.
啊，我找德芙琳大夫问问
Uh-huh.I'll page Dr. Devlin.
她接了汉森的病例
She's on the Hanson case.
这太不公平了
this is so not fair.
可不是么，你回头再找格蕾丝问罪吧
Yeah.You can thank Grace later.
我需要CT扫描
I need a C.T. scan.
再给我点止疼药
And I'm gonna need something for the pain.
我对吗啡过敏
Uh...I'm allergic to morphine.
还有一种药
There's this, um...This other drug.
叫什么酮什么的。盐酸二氢吗啡酮？
I think it's "d"-something.Dilaudid?
对，就是它
Yeah.That's the one.
这比吗啡的药效强十倍
It's 10 times more powerful than morphine.
我的疼痛也是十倍递增的
Well, I got 10 times the pain.
我给你约一个腹部骨盆CT检查，再开两剂盐酸二吗啡酮
I'll order an abdominal/pelvis C.T. and two of dilaudid.
你真是个好大夫
You're a wonderful doctor.
用不用我再给你拿个枕头或者毯子？
Would you like an extra pillow or blanket?
爸
Dad.
布雷特
Brett.
好久不见
It's been too long.
是啊，这是德芙琳大夫，杰克的外科医生
Yeah. Uh, this is Dr. Devlin,Jack's surgeon.
我只是外科医生之一
Well, one of them.
这是怀特医生，他是负责杰克这次手术的主治医生
Dr. White, chief of surgery,is handling his case personally.
马克・汉森，这是卡罗尔・古德曼
Mark Hanson.This is Carol Goodman.
这是杰克的妻子，安娜贝尔。杰克怎么样了？
Jack's wife, Annabelle.How's Jack?
目前他的血压还不太稳定
At the moment,his blood pressure is unstable.
我们现在还不能拿掉他的呼吸器
We're having some trouble weaning him off the ventilator.
所以说，可能是大脑或者脊柱损伤
So, there is a possibility of some brain or spinal injury.
哦，不
Oh, no.
我的天呐，我还以为CT扫描正常呢
Oh, my God.I thought the C.T. was normal.
CT扫描不出神经损伤
Not all neurological injuries show up on C.T.,
所以我们还想问问关于车祸的情况
So we need to know a little more about the crash.
你看见他摔了是吧？没有，但我当时在现场
You saw it happen, right? No. I was there, but no.
我听见撞车了，我跑过去叫了救护车
I heard it. I came running.I called the ambulance.
但是那是在法院门口撞的是吧？
But it happened outside the courthouse?
是啊，问这干吗？法院外边没有监控吗？
Yeah, why? Don't they have surveillance cameras?
有哇，我待会给法院打个电话问问
Yeah. Yeah, they do.I'll call the courthouse.
半小时之后就能拿到监控录像
We'll have those tapes in 30 minutes.
那，你找到想杀我的人了吗？
So...You find out who's trying to kill me yet?
哪那么容易就找着了啊
Well,it's not that simple.
我的手下已经把炸弹特征输入数据库了
Our guy put the bomb's markers through the database.
还没找到结果
No names poped up.
这种炸弹装置
The device is identical to a bomb that was used
和几年前贝尔蒙（加州）的一起餐厅爆炸案所使用的炸弹是一样的
To blow up a diner on Belmont a couple of years back.
警察找到凶手了吗？
Yeah.Cops make anyone on that?
没有
No.
贝尔蒙那家餐厅是叫皇家餐厅吗？
The place on Belmont --is it The Royal Diner?
对，就是
Yeah, that's what he said.
问这干吗？那是一起保险诈骗案
Why? It was an insurance scam.
餐厅老板想弄成种族报复案件
The owner wanted to make the bombing look racially motivated,
拿了保险赔偿之后分裂城里的帮派
Took the insurance payout,and split town.
朋友，你怎么会知道这么清楚？
And how do you know so much about this, my friend?
我调查过这个事
I may have consulted.
是吗？那是谁做的炸弹？
Yeah? Well,who built the bomb?
哦，这人你认识，吉米・倪德思
Oh, you know him.Jimmy Needles.
吉米・倪德思？就是他
Jimmy Needles? Jimmy Needles.
我跟你说，让吉尔把他找来
I'll tell you what --go have Gio pick him up.
我们得给我们的老朋友吉米・倪德思
It's time we had a little homecoming
开个欢迎会了
With our old friend Jimmy Needles.
啊
Ouch.
这只是头部轻微的撞击
It's just a glancing blow to the head.
是啊
Yeah.
对，看这，他的胳膊摔断了
Yeah, see,he fractures his arm here,
然后他就地十八滚……
And then he just...Rolls.
没摔到头
No major head trauma.
没有颈部损伤
No extreme flection or extension of his neck.
你能放大点吗？
Can you zoom in?
好，等会，停
Okay, wait, stop.
在这儿停，快看
Stop right there.Look, look, look.
看他的手
Look at his hands.
他放开了车把
He just lets go of the handlebars.
他可能在撞车之前就失去意识了
He might have lost consciousness before the crash.
咱们之前的分析都错了
We've been going about this the wrong way.
没准是神经缺损导致的创伤
Maybe a neurologic deficit caused the trauma,
不是别的原因
Not the other way around.
那么，在意识水平改变导致的头部创伤诊断之外
So, what's the differential diagnosis for A.L.O.C.
还有别的可能性吗？
Besides head trauma?
要不就是，未知毒素的发作或者脑补感染
What about, like, a weird toxin exposure or brain infection?
他以前有没有去野营或者出国旅行的经历？
Has he been camping or on any foreign trips?
噢，我们太专注于创伤治疗了，没问
Oh, we've been so focused on the trauma, we didn't ask.
他现在昏迷不醒，去
Well, he's comatose. Go.
问问他的家人
Talk to his family.
可能是大脑炎。或者是登革热？
Maybe encephalitis.How does dengue fever present?
我一点都不知道
I don't have a clue.
我得接个电话
You know what? I got to take this.
怎么了？
What?
格蕾丝，吃完你给的药马疯了！
Grace, the pills made Matty Boy worse! He's freaking out!
那马还在持续勃起呢？（priapistic―Priapism：阴茎持续勃起）
Is he still priapistic?
如果你的意思是：“他还挺着呢”，是的
If that means, "is he still sporting wood," then yes.
现在他很暴躁
Now he's all aggro.
听着，内特，我现在正忙着呢
Look, I am in the middle of something here, Nate.
格蕾丝，维克多说上礼拜
Grace,Vic told me last week
汤米・沃尔有个手下惹着他了
One of Tommy Walls' guys pissed him off.
汤米用火把把这哥们给烧死了
Tommy went after him with a blow torch, burned him to the bone.
你说他会怎么对付我呢？
What do you think he's gonna do to me?
好吧，我尽快赶过去
All right, look,I'll get there as soon as I can.
嘿，有个家伙在重症监护室把导管拔出来了
Hey. A guy in ICU just yanked out his E.T. tube.
好吧，我可以去调查杰克的病史
All right, I can get Jack's history on my own,
然后咱们再会研究
And then I'll just meet up with you later.
谢谢
Thanks.
没有，我们没去野营过
No, we haven't been camping.
北京奥运会之后我们就没出过国了
And we haven't been out of the country since 2008.
几个星期前，我们一起参加了一个法律会议
A couple of weeks ago, we went to a legal conference together.
在哪开的？
Anywhere exotic?
托莱多，机场酒店
Toledo --the airport hotel.
杰克有没有可能在飞机上被传染了什么病？
Could Jack have caught something on the plane?
不好说，我们得做一个全面的传染病检查
Maybe. We're doing a full infectious workup.
他不会有事的，对么？
He's gonna be okay.Right?
孩子，别对我们隐瞒他的病情
Just tell us the truth,son.
不会的，爸爸
I always do, dad.
杰克他……不太稳定
Jack is...Becoming less stable.
要是我们查不出病因，他就……
If we don't find out the cause, then...
他就会死？
He could die?
哦，天呐
Oh, God.
安娜贝尔，我们会尽最大努力的
A-Annabelle, we're doing everything we can.
我得去给杰克做检查了
I-I'm gonna go check on Jack.
别害怕，哥们，别害怕
Easy, buddy.Easy, easy.
不，不，不，没事，没事
No, no, no.It's okay. It's okay.
不，我……我正在换轮胎
No, I'm, uh...No,I'm changing the tire right now.
我们会把马蒂小子及时送到测试场的
I'm gonna get Matty Boy to the track on time.
不用担心
Don't sweat it.
我给咱们争取了个把小时的时间
all right, I bought us one hour, maybe two tops.
要是还搞不定，汤米就知道这件事了
After that,Tommy's gonna know what's up.
谢天谢地
Thank God.
嘿，赶紧给他看看吧
Hey, take your time, why don't you?
这马怎么了？
What's wrong with him?
他上次撒尿是什么时候？
When was the last time he urinated?
他没尿
He hasn't.
他需要阴茎注射苯肾上腺素（一种血管收缩剂）
He needs an intracavernosal injection of phenylephrine.
什么玩意儿？
A what now?
我得先给他打一针克他命（一种强效麻醉剂）让他平静下来
I got to tranquilize him with ketamine
让他把阴茎里的血排出来。喔！喔！
And drain the blood from his penis. Whoa, whoa.
这匹马明天还有比赛呢
This horse has to race tomorrow,
测试场会把所有的药物都检查出来的
And the track is gonna test for performance enhancers, all of that.
克他命是一种镇静剂，不是兴奋剂，所以，应该没事
Well, ketamine's a downer, not an upper, so we should be fine.
那笨什么素是干吗用的？苯肾上腺素
What about the phenyl...Ephen? Phenylephrine.
尿检会查出来吗？
Is it gonna show up in a urine test?
我也不知道，他们都查什么，内特
I don't know what they test for, Nate.
那我们就没法让他比赛了
Then we can't risk it.
格蕾丝
Grace.
在马骑到充气娃娃上之后
After the horse mounted the, uh...Dummy mare,
你们到底是怎么取精液的？
How were you actually gonna collect the sperm?
那东西叫人造阴道
Well, it's called an artificial vagina.
让我瞧瞧
Let me see it.
这就是充了水的橡胶管
It's just rubber tubing filled with water,
但是我们没用上
But we didn't get to use it.
好吧，给我拿个冰袋来。干吗使啊？
Okay, get me a bag of ice. Why?
我要用物理方法让这匹马“降温”
Because I need a noninvasive way to help the horse.
你要有别的问题吗？
Do you have any other questions?
你呼的我？
You paged me?
腹部CT结果出来了
Abdominal C.T.
看看肠系膜上动脉的栓塞
Check out the clot in the superior mesenteric artery.
严重血栓症，这是谁的CT结果？
Acute thrombosis.Who's C.T. is this?
我们的常客
Our frequent flyer.
真的假的？
You're kidding?
这回她是真病了
She actually has something wrong this time.
她的肠部坏死，不动手术她会死的
Her bowel's necrosing.Without surgery, she'll die.
德芙琳大夫误诊了
Dr. Devlin missed it.
还让我承担这个结果，就是这么回事
And I caught it.That's all that matters.
吉米！哈？
Jimmy! Huh?
吉米・倪德思
Jimmy Needles.
别来无恙啊
Long time, no see.
你看上去不是特别好哇，吉米
You're not looking too good there, Jimmy.
我发誓，我不知道他们把炸弹寄给你了
I swear...I -- I didn't know that they'd send you that bomb.
你说什么？
What was that you said?
他们？他们是谁啊？吉米？
"they"? Who's "they," Jimmy?
我从来不跟客户见面
I never meet my customers.
我有个预约系统
I got a booking system.
我的客户会得到一个三位的密码，然后他们把现金给我
My customers get a three-digit code, and they leave me cash.
他说他把一个包放在简诺拉公园的长椅下边
Says he dropped a package under a bench in Janura Park.
我说的都是真的
I'm telling the truth.
好吧，我相信你
All right,I believe you.
这么说，你这个客户的号码是什么？
So, what number is your buyer?
4-4-7.
但是我不知道这个客户是谁，我也不想知道
But I don't know who that is.I don't want to know.
这就是我们交易的方法
That's the way it works.
这么说倒是很合理，知道吗，吉米？
I mean, you know, that makes sense to me, Jimmy, you know?
用谨慎的交易方式寻找你的客户
Discreet business practice,looking out for your customers.
啊！你给我听好
Aah! You listen to me.
你得把我想知道的都告诉我
You're gonna tell me what I want to know,
否则我就打碎你的脑袋就像打碎一个椰子
Or I'm gonna crack your head open like a coconut
然后拿你喂狗
And feed you to my dogs!
安马拓兄弟
The Amato brothers.
你想骗我？
are you lying to me?
4-4-7……那就是安马拓兄弟的代号
4-4-7...That's the Amato brothers.
他们雇的我
They hired me.
我发誓
I swear.
巴闭，给他松绑
Bobby, cut him loose.
把他扔到小巷的垃圾堆里去
Throw him out in the alley with the rest of the garbage.
你救了丹蒂的名，他就这么报答你？
You saved Dante's life,and this is how they repay you?
嘿，安马拓就是这么贪婪
Hey, the Amatos were always greedy pigs.
他们认为跟着就能得到整个地盘
They figured with me gone,they can get the whole pie.
要不我召集一个会议？
Want me to set up a meeting?
不，不能再谈了
No. No more talk.
格蕾丝，冰都快化了
Grace, the ice is starting to melt.
很好，那你就再把它填满
Good, then you can refill it.
他是在装死吗？
What,is he playing dead?
他睡着了
He's sedated.
维克，我的手都快冻僵了
Vic, my hand is starting to freeze.
你接着弄吧
Take over.
嘿，大夫，我觉得这方法起作用了
Hey, Doc,I think it's working.
妈的，我姐棒不棒？
Damn, is my sister good or what?
嘿，维克，抓紧了
Hey, Vic.Hang on tight.
嘿，嘿！
Hey, hey!
这张不错
good one, man.
喔，喔，喔
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
你觉着有意思吗？
You think that's funny?
小子，你知道我为谁工作吗？
Dude,you know who I work for?
我觉得还是算了，维克多
I -- I think you should walk away, Victor.
维克多，走开
Victor, walk away.
有这么个姐姐算你走运，手淫去吧
You're lucky she's your sister, jackoff.
听我说，我知道我搞砸了
Look...I know I screwed up, okay?
但是咱们能跳过沉默阶段
But can we just, like,skip the silent treatment
直接骂我一顿得了
And get to the part where you yell at me?
你知道吗？
You know what?
现在，布雷特的弟弟正在重症监护室
Right now,Brett's brother is in the ICU.
而我却又被拉到这儿来处理你这些破事儿
And instead of being there,I am dealing with your crap again.
你能不能成熟点啊
You have got to grow up.
我也不是没干正经事啊
I'm part of something right now.
这事要是能行的话
I-if this had worked --
要是这事能行？
"if this had worked"?
内特，你不会这么蠢吧
Come on, Nate.You know better.
谢谢
Thanks.
你完全可以跟我说不给我药，对吧？
You could have just said no to the meds, all right?
还有很多别的医院可以去
There are plenty of other hospitals.
你得了肠系膜血管血栓
You have a mesenteric thrombosis.
就跟我知道那是什么意思似的
Like I'm supposed to know what that means.
意思是，如果你不做手术就会死
It means that without surgery,you will die.
你真不会撒谎，大夫
You're a bad liar, Doc.
好吧
Fine.
反正要死的人是你
It's your funeral.
那你就签个“不遵医嘱”的表格吧
Just read and sign this "against medical advice" form
我好留个证据
While I get a witness.
留证据干吗？
You need a witness for what?
我解释过不配合治疗的
That I explained the consequences
的严重后果了
Of denying the recommended treatment.
一会见吧
See you later.
等等
Wait.
如果我同意手术，能给我一些吗啡酮吗？
If I agree to the surgery,can I have some more dilaudid?
对刺激测试毫无反应
No response to painful stimuli at all.
毫无进展
It's progressing.
没准做个脊椎抽液能发现点新情况
Well, maybe something will show during the spinal tap.
看见了吗？
Have you seen this?
那是皮肉擦伤吗？他当时穿了衣服的啊
Is that road rash? He was wearing a suit.
触感很软，你觉得会不会是皮下脓肿？
Boggy to the touch. You think there's an abscess underneath?
你把紫外线灯递给我
Will you hand me that wood's lamp over there?
是真菌感染？
Thinking fungal infection?
如果是的话会在紫外线灯下能显示出来
If it is, it'll show up under the black light.
不是真菌
It's not fungus.
是“卡罗尔”
It's "Carol."
布雷特？卡罗尔
Brett? Carol.
我看见你呼我了
Um...I had you paged.
我们得谈谈
We need to...talk.
怎么了？
What's going on?
你知道杰克的纹身吗？
Do you know anything about Jack's tattoo?
哦，天呐
Oh, God.
你是不是跟我弟弟有过那么一段？
Are -- are you having an affair with my brother?
卡罗尔，你从他很小的时候就认识他
Carol, you've...known him since he was a kid,
而且你还是他的老板
And you're his boss.
我们也不知道会那样
We didn't mean for it to happen.
听着，那个纹身被感染了
Look, the --the tattoo's infected.
我想知道他是在哪纹的
I need to know where he got it.
巴巴多斯岛（西印度群岛中的岛屿，度假胜地）
Barbados.
那是一家布里奇顿（巴巴多斯岛首都）的纹身店
It's a tattoo parlor in Bridgetown
他们专门纹只有通过紫外线能看到的纹身
Where they specialize in U.V. tattoos.
他什么时候纹的？
When did he get it?
九天之前
Nine days ago.
这么说，你们根本没再托莱多开会对么？
So, you weren't at a conference in Toledo?
没有
No.
布莱特，自从你妈妈去世之后
Brett...After your mother passed,
杰克连个说心里话的人都没有
Jack had no one else that he could talk to.
他妻子不是吗？
How about his wife?
他根本就没想跟安娜贝尔结婚
He never wanted to marry Annabelle.
那是你爸爸的决定
That was your father's pick.
你知道么，杰克做的每一件事
All right, you know that everything that Jack does,
都是你爸爸在幕后操纵的
Your father pulls the strings.
为什么你觉得他这么卑鄙？
Why do you think he's so miserable?
我不知道他是这样的
I didn't know he was.
自从你离开，你爸爸就把原本想让你干的事
Since you left, everything your father wanted for you --
全都压在杰克身上
Now it's on Jack.
现在你怎么想我都没关系，但是，求你
Now, you can think what you want about me, but, please...
别让他死
...Don't let him die.
骨头！
Bones!
嘿，骨头，过来，小子！
yo, Bones! Come here, boy!
骨头！
Bones!
嘿，别又把鞋叼走了
Hey, that better not be another shoe.
卧槽得嘞！
What the hell? Ugh!
为什么？你脑子有病！
Why, you lame brain!
来一杯威士忌？
You want a whiskey?
我得回家了
I got to drive home.
你在这失败了
So, you crash here.
为什么我会在这失败
Why would I want to crash here
我还有个湖边小屋能待着，啊？
When I got a lake house to stay in, huh?
你是跟这躲事儿来了
You're the one who's in hiding.
杂种
Bastard.
别这么说妈妈
Don't talk about mom that way.
怎回事？
the hell?
嘿！
Hey.
伙计们，最近怎么样？你们看什么呢？
Fellas, how's it going? What are you watching?
哦，三头呆鹅
Oh, the three stooges.
我喜欢丑角儿，哈？很好。
I love the stooges, huh? It's appropriate.
两个小丑坐在电视机前看丑角儿
A couple of clowns sitting around watching the stooges.
坐下
Sit down.
知道么，我对你们很失望
I want you guys to know I'm disappointed in you.
你，我救过你的命
You --I saved your life.
还有你，你们俩，我来跟你们做生意
And you -- both of you --I came up with a deal
能让你们赚大钱的生意
That's gonna make you a whole bunch of money.
然后你们居然这么对我，啊？
And this is what you do to me, huh?
你出卖我，还想杀我？
You set me up? You try to kill me?
你像个胆小鬼一样给我送来一颗炸弹
You send me a pipe bomb like some coward?
你什么意思？
What are you talking about?
你说是我送的炸弹？
You're telling --you're saying we sent the bomb?
胡说八道
That's --that's insane.
我能证明不是我们干的，你看这桌子上都摆着呢
I can prove it wasn't us.Look on the table here.
这是咱们的游戏机合同
It's our contract for the gaming machines.
在你被送炸弹之前
I signed them over to you two weeks ago --
我就签好了合同了
Before you got sent that bomb.
那又怎样？
So what?
那就意味着甭管你是不是死了，那些机器都属于你们公司的
So your company owns the rights to the machines even if you die.
我为什么要杀你呢，我需要你
Why would I kill you? I need you.
那你是什么意思？
So, what are you saying?
你最近还没跟吉米・倪德思做成生意呢？
You haven't done any business with Jimmy Needles lately?
那也不是去炸你的餐馆啊
Not to blow up your place.
你的代号是不是4-4-7？
And your code's not 4-4-7?
怎么了？你看我干吗？
What? What are you looking at?
那是我们的代码
That's our number.
我什么也没干。他撒谎
I didn't do anything.He's lying!
他没必要说谎，他手里攥着枪呢
He doesn't have to lie.He's holding a gun.
嘿，听我说
Hey, come on.Come on. Come on.
你怎么看？
What about you?
我从来不想做这笔生意
I never liked the terms of our deal.
但是我默许了
But I accepted them.
我哥哥，做事太不小心
My brother --he didn't feel that way.
我从来没想过把你干掉
I never thought he would try to take you out.
我信你
I believe you.
真的，我信
Really, I do.
那么，下一步你想怎么办？
So,what's your next move?
我把他埋了，如果我们还在同一阵营的话
I'm gonna bury him outside, and if you and I are square...
那我们就继续做生意
...Then we're back in business.
当然，不过我要把你哥哥那份拿走
Of course, I'm gonna be absorbing your brother's shares.
我相信他会理解的
I'm sure he would understand.
那么，我们达成一致了？
So, we square?
是的
yeah.
请节哀
Sorry for your loss.
可能是通过未清洗的纹身针感染的
The infection could be from a dirty tatoo needle.
抗药金黄葡萄球菌？有可能
M.R.S.A.? Can't be.
不发烧，白血球数量正常
No fever,normal white count.
没有发炎迹象
There's no evidence of cellulitis.
筋膜炎坏死？
Necrotizing fasciitis?
那不足以解释为什么神经缺损
That doesn't explain the neuro deficits.
会不会是肉毒杆菌？
What about botulism?
我是说，症状吻合
I mean, the symptoms fit --
虚弱，伴随倾斜性瘫痪
Weakness,then descending paralysis.
眼睛，上呼吸系统，然后是四肢
Eyes, respiratory, upper,then lower extremities,
而且我们还找到了病原
And we have a source.
是，非常好，我们怎么确认它呢？
Yes, very good.How do we confirm it?
创伤培养
Culture the wound.
哦，送去做个肉毒杆菌化验
Uh, send out for a botulism assay.
等化验期间，我们再给他打大剂量的抗毒素
In the meantime, we'll dose him with heavy antitoxin.
就这么干
Do it.
嘿，格蕾丝
Hey. Grace.
你还记得今天早上你看的那个病人吗？提芬尼・埃文斯
You remember that patient you saw this morning, Tiffany Evans?
记得，谎报病情，嗜药成瘾，怎么了？
Yeah, the addict who cries wolf. Why?
你误诊了，那是肠系膜动脉血栓
You missed a mesenteric artery thrombosis.
你做了CT检查？做了
You did a C.T.? Yeah.
我做了血栓切除术
And then I performed a thrombectomy.
她现在没事了
She's in recovery.
喔，你救了她一命
Wow. Then you saved her life.
除此之外，你还想跟我说什么
Not that you'll rub that in or anything.
是啊，也许有点想说的
Yeah,maybe a little bit.
天哪，这是第一次我站在她面前的时候命运捉弄了我
God, the one time I stand up to her, fate screws me.
但这次命运把咱们俩都捉弄了
But this time fate screwed us both.
她把你评定为服务不及格？
She flunked you on the survey?
手术之后，我把她推荐给一位疼痛处理专家
Post-surgery,I recommended her
为了解除对吗啡酮的药瘾
To a pain-management specialist，who took her off dilaudid.
嘿
Hey.
联邦法院就在那
Federal courthouse is right over there.
我爸曾经管它叫他的网球场
Dad used to call it his tennis court.
我和杰克管他叫麦肯罗，因为他允许我们逃学
Jack and I called him McEnroe 'cause he'd let us skip school
去看他和国防部律师在那擦地
To come watch him mop the floor with sleazy defense attorneys.
听上去你挺欣赏他
Sounds like you admired him.
那时候年轻
I was young.
六年之后，我妈被查出来乳房长了个肿块
Six years ago, my mother found a lump on her breast.
癌症
It was... Cancer.
我爸爸让她延迟化疗时间
And my dad asked her to delay chemo
直到他得到听证会的结果
Until after his confirmation hearings
那样就不会
So that there wouldn't be the perception
让他在工作上分心
That he was distracted.
哦
Oh.
结果，她没有遵医嘱，延迟了五个星期
So, she delayed... Five weeks,against doctors' orders,
然后淋巴结扩散了
And it... Spread...To her lymph nodes.
我爸在她的葬礼上念了悼文
My dad gave the eulogy at her funeral.
他说我妈是他的灵魂伴侣
He said that she was his soul mate,
是他一生的挚爱
That she was the love of his life,
然后他哭了，然后上了时代周刊的封面
And then he cried... And made the cover of Time magazine...
这个封面被镶上了镜框挂在他的办公室
Which is now framed in his office.
干得好，鲁滨逊大夫
Good save,Dr. Robinson.
你弟弟对肉毒杆菌抗菌素
Your brother's responding to the botulism antitoxin
和抗生素有了反应
And antibiotics.
他已经可以拔掉呼吸器了
He's already off the vent.
抢救我还挺费劲的，哈？
I must have bit it hard, huh?
你的腕部骨折
compound wrist fracture.
我们必须得给你打了一颗钢钉
Ortho had to put a pin in it,so no, uh, strumming it
八周之后才能痊愈
For at least eight weeks,okay?
没事，我左右手都很灵活
Good thing I'm ambidextrous.
你的喉咙会因为插了呼吸管道有点疼
Your, uh, throat's gonna be sore from being intubated.
你感染了肉毒杆菌
So, you had a wound botulism.
这就是你昏迷摔倒的原因
That's why you lost control and crashed.
肉毒杆菌？
Botulism?
是从未消毒的纹身针上传染的
From a dirty tattoo needle.
纹身还在
It's...Still there.
都谁知道这事了？
Who knows?
只有卡罗尔，还有你的医生
Just Carol...And your doctors.
好吧，你说吧
So, let's hear it.
说出来，你很震惊
Let's hear it.You're shocked.
你对我失望了
You're disappointed.
我很抱歉
No. I'm sorry, Jack.
只是很抱歉
Just... Sorry.
为什么？因为我过着你原本该过的生活？
For what? For living your life?
为了你离开爸爸道歉？
For getting the hell away from dad?
我真希望我有你一半的勇气
I wish I had half your guts.
现在怎么办？
So, what now?
你要接受十天的抗生素治疗
You're on a 10-day regimen of antibiotics.
不是，我说的是家人
No, I meant with the family.
他们会问一些问题
They're gonna ask questions.
你想让我怎么回答？
What do you want me to do?
他可能是开玉米罐头的时候
It's possible that he contracted the botulism
感染了肉毒杆菌，不过他不会有事的
From a dented can of corn, but he's gonna be okay.
你救了我儿子一命，大夫
You saved my son's life,doctor.
如果有什么我能帮得上忙的话
If there's ever anything you need...
哦，这是我们的职责
Oh, it's --it's what we do.
别跟我们疏远了，好吗？
Don't be such a stranger, okay?
好的
Okay.
谢谢你
Thank you.
回见
Catch you later.
好的
Okay.
好了，我该走了
All right,I should be going.
等等，孩子
Wait. Wait, son.
我知道杰克没去托莱多
I know Jack wasn't in Toledo.
我为你在家里主事的那种状态而自豪
I'm proud of the way you handled things -- with the family.
爸，我不是对你撒谎
Dad,I didn't lie for you.
我是因为你才撒谎的
I lied because of you.
我想你肯定很渴
I thought you might be thirsty.
我给你买了个礼物
I brought you a gift.
哦，你的幽默感太怪了
Oh, you've got a sick sense of humor.
咱俩都一样
we both do.
哦，是吗？
Oh, yeah?
砰
Boom.
真可笑。哦，还挺凉的
Very funny.Oh, it's cold.
我听斯塔沃斯说你处理到了那个送炸弹的人
So, Stavos told me you took care of the bomber.
是我认识的人吗？
Do I know him?
是，丹蒂・安马拓
Yeah. Dante Amato.
这孙子居然背着他弟弟干这种事
And the bastard was even keeping it secret from his brother.
嗯
Hmm.
知道么，这是笔可笑的生意
You know,it's a funny business.
我们俩曾经是好朋友
He and I used to be good friends.
我觉得你应该说句祝酒词
I think you should propose a toast.
哦，是吗？
Oh, yeah?
为什么不呢？
Why not?
你有很多需要感谢的话要说
You got so much to be thankful for.
好吧，敬你脑子里想的那些事
Well, here's to what you got on your mind.
对不起
Sorry.
现在不行，吉尔
Not now, Gio.
有人来找你了，头儿，他说有要紧的事
Somebody's here to see you,boss -- tells me it's urgent.
好吧，让他进来
All right.Let him in.
我搜过他了，没事
He's clean.
我得私下里跟你谈谈
I need to talk to you --in private.
这人是谁啊？
Who the hell is this guy?
我从来没见过你
I've never seen you before.
好久没见了
It's been a long time.
告诉你吧，小子
Let me tell you something, kid.
我从来不会忘记任何一张脸
I never forget a face.
那你再近看看
Then look closer.
是我啊，爸爸
It's me, dad.
Thinks for watch! subtitle Translation by @godort